Guide to the Charles Edward Clark Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- United States Court of Appeals for the Second District, 1939-1963; Series II; 23' (55 boxes)
  - Case Files
    - 1948-1949 A-F (Box 35, Folder 91)
    - 1948-1949 G-M (Box 35, Folder 92)
    - 1948-1949 N-S (Box 35, Folder 93)
    - 1948-1949 T-Z (Box 35, Folder 94)
    - 1948-1949 T-Z (Box 35, Folder 95)
    - 1949-1950 A-F (Box 36, Folder 96)
    - 1949-1950 G-M (Box 36, Folder 97)
    - 1949-1950 N-S (Box 36, Folder 98)
    - 1949-1950 T-Z (Box 36, Folder 99)
    - 1950-1951 A-F (Box 36, Folder 100)
    - 1950-1951 G-M (Box 36, Folder 101)
    - 1950-1951 N-R (Box 36, Folder 102)
    - 1950-1951 S-U (Box 36, Folder 103)
    - 1950-1951 V-Z (Box 36, Folder 104)
    - 1951-1952 A-E (Box 36, Folder 105)
    - 1951-1952 F-L (Box 36, Folder 106)
    - 1951-1952 Mc-R (Box 37, Folder 107)
    - 1951-1952 S-U (empty) (Box 37, Folder 108)
    - 1951-1952 W-Z (Box 37, Folder 109)
    - 1952-1953 A-E (Box 37, Folder 110)
    - 1952-1953 F-K (Box 37, Folder 111)
    - 1952-1953 L-Q (Box 37, Folder 112)
    - 1952-1953 R-T (Box 37, Folder 113)
    - 1952-1953 U-Z (Box 37, Folder 114)
    - 1953-1954 A-E (Box 37, Folder 115)
    - 1953-1954 F-L (Box 37, Folder 116)
    - 1953-1954 M-R (Box 37, Folder 117)
    - 1953-1954 S-U (empty) (Box 37, Folder 118)
    - 1953-1954 V-Z (Box 38, Folder 119)
    - 1954-1955 A-E (Box 38, Folder 120)
    - 1954-1955 F-L (Box 38, Folder 121)
    - 1954-1955 Q-T (Box 38, Folder 122)
    - 1954-1955 U-Z (Box 38, Folder 123)
    - 1955-1956 A-E (Box 38, Folder 124)
    - 1955-1956 F-L (Box 38, Folder 125)
    - 1955-1956 Mc-R (Box 38, Folder 126)
    - 1955-1956 S-T (Box 38, Folder 127)
    - 1955-1956 U-U.S. v. Nunan (Box 39, Folder 128-129)
    - 1955-1956 U.S. v. Nunan-Z (Box 39, Folder 130)
    - 1956-1957 A-E (Box 39, Folder 131)
    - 1956-1957 F-K (empty) (Box 39, Folder 132)
    - 1956-1957 L-O (Box 39, Folder 133)
    - 1956-1957 P-T (Box 39, Folder 134)
    - 1956-1957 U-U.S. v. G (Box 39, Folder 135-136)
    - 1956-1957 U.S. v. G-U.S. v. Q (Box 40, Folder 137)
    - 1956-1957 U.S. v. R-U.S. v. W (Box 40, Folder 138-139)
    - 1956-1957 U.S. ex rel-end of U (Box 40, Folder 140)
    - 1956-1957 V-Z (Box 40, Folder 141)
    - 1957-1958 A-B (Box 40, Folder 142)
    - 1957-1958 A-B (Box 40, Folder 143)
    - 1957-1958 C-K (empty) (Box 41, Folder 144)
    - 1957-1958 L-Q (Box 41, Folder 145)
    - 1957-1958 R-T (Box 41, Folder 146)
    - 1957-1958 U-U.S. v. K (Box 41, Folder 147-148)
    - 1957-1958 U.S. v. L (Box 41, Folder 149)
    - 1957-1958 U.S. v. L-end of U (Box 41, Folder 150)
    - 1957-1958 V-Z (Box 41, Folder 151)
    - 1958-1959 A-B (Box 41, Folder 152-153)
    - 1958-1959 C-K (empty) (Box 42, Folder 154)
    - 1958-1959 L-Q (Box 42, Folder 155)
    - 1958-1959 R-S (Box 42, Folder 156-157)
    - 1958-1959 T-U (Box 42, Folder 158)
    - 1958-1959 V-Z (Box 42, Folder 159)
    - 1959-1960 A-K (Box 42, Folder 160)
    - 1959-1960 L-P (Box 42, Folder 161-162)
    - 1959-1960 Q-T (Box 42, Folder 163)
    - 1959-1960 T-U.S. v. Gori (Box 43, Folder 164)
    - 1959-1960 U.S. v. Gori-U.S. v. Llamas (Box 43, Folder 165)
    - 1959-1960 U.S. v. Magyar-U.S. ex rel v. We Shung (Box 43, Folder 166)
    - 1959-1960 U.S. ex rel v. Williams-Z (Box 43, Folder 167)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 168)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 169)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 43, Folder 170)
    - Pre-conference memoranda, 1939-1939 - 1953-1954 (Box 44, Folder 171)
    - Memos, 1962-1963 (Box 44, Folder 172-174)
    - A, 1952-1956, 1960-1963 (Box 44, Folder 175-179)
    - B, 1942-1956, 1960-1962 (Box 45, Folder 180-187)
    - B, 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 188)
    - C, 1938-1943, 1956-1962 (Box 46, Folder 189-194)
    - D, 1954-1956 (Box 46, Folder 195)
    - D, 1954-1963 (Box 47, Folder 196-198)
    - E, 1948-1962 (Box 47, Folder 199-201)
    - F, 1938-1956 (Box 47, Folder 202-204)
    - F, 1956-1962 (Box 48, Folder 205-207)
    - Fitzgerald v. U.S. Lines Co., 1961-1962 (Box 48, Folder 208)
    - F, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 209)
    - Farrand Optical Co. v. U.S., Oct 1962 term (Box 48, Folder 210)
    - Farmer v. Arabian American Oil Co., Oct 1962 term (Box 48, Folder 211)
    - G, 1945-1953 (Box 48, Folder 212-213)
    - G, 1956-1963 (Box 49, Folder 214-217)
    - H, 1956-1963 (Box 49, Folder 218-219)
    - I, 1956-1962 (Box 49, Folder 220)
    - J, 1956-1962 (Box 50, Folder 221)
    - K, 1938-1963 (Box 50, Folder 222-225)
    - L, 1960-1963 (Box 50, Folder 226)
    - Mc, 1960-1963 (Box 50, Folder 227)
    - M, 1938-1943 (Box 50, Folder 228-229)
    - M, 1943-1956, 1960-1963 (Box 51, Folder 230-235)
    - N, 1938-1943 (Box 51, Folder 236-237)
    - N, 1943-1956, 1960-1963 (Box 52, Folder 238-244)
    - P, 1956-1961 (Box 53, Folder 245-246)
    - Pugach v. Dollinger, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 247)
    - P, 1961-1963 (Box 53, Folder 248)
    - Pearson v. N.E. Airlines Inc., 1962 (Box 53, Folder 249)
    - R, 1956-1963 (Box 53, Folder 250-251)
    - S, 1938-1942 (Box 53, Folder 252-253)
    - S, 1942-1654, 1959-1963 (Box 54, Folder 254-261)
    - S.E.C. v. Capital Gains Research Bureau, Inc., 1962 (Box 55, Folder 262)
    - T, 1938-1956 (Box 55, Folder 263-265)
    - U, 1950-1952, 1954-1955 (Box 55, Folder 266-269)
    - U, 1958-1959 (Box 56, Folder 270-272)
    - U.S. v. Bufalino, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 273)
    - U.S. v. Santore, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 274)
    - U, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 275-277)
    - U.S. ex rel Reid v. Richmond, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 278)
    - U, 1961-1963 (Box 57, Folder 279-284)
    - XYZ, 1938-1956 (Box 57, Folder 285)
  - Motion Files
    - 1938-1939 - 1944-1945 (Box 58, Folder 286-287)
    - 1945-1955 (Box 58, Folder 288-292)
    - 1952-1955 (Box 59, Folder 293)
    - Motion Calendars, 1952-1955 (Box 59, Folder 294)
    - 1955-1958 (Box 59, Folder 295-299)
    - 1958-1959, A-U (Box 60, Folder 300-301)
    - 1958-1959, U-Z (Box 60, Folder 302-303)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 304-307)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 61, Folder 308-314)
    - In re Chopak, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 315)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 62, Folder 316-318)
    - Homeless (Misc.) (Box 62, Folder 319)
  - Correspondence with Court of Appeals Judges
    - Chase, Harrie B. (Box 63, Folder 320)
    - Frank, Jerome N. (Box 63, Folder 321-324)
    - Friendly, Henry J. (Box 63, Folder 325)
    - Hand, Augustus N. (Box 63, Folder 326)
    - Hand, Learned, 1939-1951, 1953-1963 (Box 63, Folder 327-329)
    - Hand, Learned Memorial Book (Box 64, Folder 330)
    - Harlan, John M. (Box 64, Folder 331)
    - Hays, Paul R. (Box 64, Folder 332)
    - Hincks, Carroll C. (Box 64, Folder 333)
    - Kaufman, Irving R. (Box 64, Folder 334)
    - Lumbard, J. Edward, 1955-1962 (Box 64, Folder 335-340)
    - Lumbard, J. Edward, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 341-343)
    - Marshall, Thurgood (Box 65, Folder 344)
    - Medina, Harold R. (Box 65, Folder 345)
    - Moore, Leonard P. (Box 65, Folder 346)
    - Smith, J. Joseph (Box 65, Folder 347)
    - Swan, Thomas W. (Box 65, Folder 348)
    - Waterman, Sterry R. (Box 65, Folder 349)
  - General Court Business Correspondence
    - 1939-1948 (Box 66, Folder 350-355)
    - 1948-1954 (Box 67, Folder 356-361)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 362)
    - 1954-1955 (August-November 1954) (Box 68, Folder 363)
    - 1954-1955 (November 1954-January 1955) (Box 68, Folder 364)
    - 1954-1955 (February 1955) (Box 68, Folder 365-366)
    - 1954-1955 (March 1955) (Box 68, Folder 367)
    - 1954-1955 (April-June 1955) (Box 69, Folder 368-369)
    - 1954-1955 (July-September 1955) (Box 69, Folder 370)
    - 1955-1956 (October 1955-January 1956) (Box 69, Folder 371)
    - 1955-1956 (February-May 1956) (Box 69, Folder 372-373)
    - 1955-1956 (June-September 1956) (Box 69, Folder 374)
    - 1956-1957 (October 1956-February 1957) (Box 69, Folder 375)
    - 1956-1957 (October 1956-February 1957) (Box 70, Folder 376)
    - 1956-1957 (March-September 1957) (Box 70, Folder 377)
    - 1957-1958 (October 1957-March 1958) (Box 70, Folder 378-379)
    - 1957-1958 (April-July 1958) (Box 70, Folder 380)
    - 1957-1958 (August-September 1958) (Box 70, Folder 381)
    - 1957-1958 (August-September 1958) (Box 70, Folder 382)
    - 1958-1959 (October 1958-January 1959) (Box 71, Folder 383)
    - 1958-1959 (February 1959-June 1959) (Box 71, Folder 384)
    - 1958-1959 (July 1959-October 1959) (Box 71, Folder 385)
    - 1959-1960 (October 1959-August 1960) (Box 71, Folder 386)
    - 1960-1963 (Box 71, Folder 387-388)
  - Circuit Council
    - 1954-1963 (Box 72, Folder 389-394)
  - Judicial Conference
    - Programs, 1955-1963 (Box 73, Folder 395)
    - 1960-1963 (Box 73, Folder 396-399)
  - Law Clerks
    - Ayer, Douglas R. Index, (1962-1963) (Box 74, Folder 400)
    - Braden, George D., (1941-1942) (Box 74, Folder 401)
    - Cudahy, Richard D., (1955-1956) (Box 74, Folder 402)
    - Cutler, Lloyd N., (1939-1940) (Box 74, Folder 403)
    - Donworth, Robert B. Jr., (1950-1951) (Box 74, Folder 404)
    - Gallen, Alvin, (1946-1947) (Box 74, Folder 405)
    - Haber, David, (1944-1945) (Box 74, Folder 406)
    - Harris, Robert J., (1950-1957) (Box 74, Folder 407)
    - Heyman, Ira Michael, (1957-1958) (Box 74, Folder 408)
    - Horan, Elizabeth R., (1939) (Box 74, Folder 409)
    - Jennings, William M., (1943-1944) (Box 74, Folder 410)
    - Kerins, Paul, (1947-1948) (Box 74, Folder 411)
    - Lee, William O'Donnell, (1942-1943) (Box 74, Folder 412)
    - Nassau, Michael J., (1960-1961) (Box 74, Folder 413)
    - Peters, Mrs. Ellen, (1954-1955) (Box 74, Folder 414)
    - Price, Karl R., (1940-1941) (Box 74, Folder 415)
    - Randolph, Francis Jr., (1953-1954) (Box 74, Folder 416)
    - Reasoner, Harry M., (1963-1964) (Box 74, Folder 417)
    - Rogers, William O., (1951-1952) (Box 74, Folder 418)
    - Ryan, Winifred R., (1945-1946) (Box 74, Folder 419)
    - Sheehan, Lawrence J., (1959-1960) (Box 74, Folder 420)
    - Stern, Lewis A., (1958-1959) (Box 75, Folder 421)
    - Trubek, David M., (1961-1962) (Box 75, Folder 422)
    - Weiss, George A., (1952-1953) (Box 75, Folder 423)
    - Wright, Charles Allen, (1949-1950) (Box 75, Folder 424)
    - Yarmolinsky, Adam, (1948-1949) (Box 75, Folder 425)
- Research files, 1929-1963; Series III; 7' (18 boxes)
  The materials in Series III are arranged in twelve sections:
  Law administration, 1929-1933
  Social trends, 1930-1933
  Automobile accidents, 1929-1933
  Connecticut Commission on the Reorganization of State Departments, 1935-1936
  Connecticut Legislative Commission on Jails, 1931-1935
  American Bar Association, Coordination Committee, 1934-1935
  American Bar Association, Committee on Co-operation with the Bench and Bar, 1934-1936
  Puerto Rican courts, 1949-1963
  Connecticut Commission on State Government Reorganization, 1949-1951
  Institute of Judicial Administration, 1953-1963
  Miscellaneous topics
  - National Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement, Law Administration Study: Correspondence & memoranda
    - 1929-1932 (Box 76, Folder 1-6)
    - 1932 (Box 77, Folder 7-8)
    - Civil Report 1933 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Report 1933 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Federal Court Study 1934 (Box 77, Folder 11-12)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Social Trends: Correspondence and memoranda
    - 1930-1933 (Box 78, Folder 14-18)
  - Automobile Accidents: Correspondence and memoranda
    - 1929-1933 (Box 79, Folder 19-24)
  - Connecticut State Executive Departments Reorganization: correspondence and memoranda
    - 1935-1936 (Box 80, Folder 25-27A)
  - Connecticut Legislative Commission on Jails: correspondence and memoranda
    - 1931-1938 (Box 80, Folder 27B-27C)
  - American Bar Association, Coordination Committee: correspondence and memoranda
    - 1934-1935 (Box 81, Folder 28-30)
  - American Bar Association, Committee on Cooperation with the Bench and Bar: correspondence and memoranda
    - 1935-1936 (Box 82, Folder 31-33)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 83, Folder 34-36)
    - 1936 (Box 84, Folder 37-38)
  - Puerto Rican Courts: correspondence and memoranda
    - 1949-1963 (Box 85, Folder 39-43)
  - Commission on Connecticut State Government Reorganization, Connecticut Courts: correspondence and memoranda
    - 1949-1951 (Box 86, Folder 44-47)
    - Reports (Box 86, Folder 48)
    - Reports (Box 87, Folder 49)
    - Final Report (Box 87, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 51-52)
  - Institute of Judicial Administration: correspondence and memoranda
    - 1953-1954 (Box 87, Folder 53-54)
    - 1955-1962 (Box 88, Folder 55-59)
    - 1963 (Box 89, Folder 60-62)
  - Miscellaneous Topics
    - Judicial Council, 1927-1930 (Box 90, Folder 63-65)
    - Business of the Federal Courts, 1934-1935 (Box 90, Folder 66-67)
    - Restatement of the Law of Property, 1924-1929 (Box 91, Folder 68-71)
    - Supreme Court, Judicial Administration, 1938-1949 (Box 91, Folder 72-73)
    - Roosevelt's Court Plan Statements, comments, 1937 (Box 91, Folder 74)
    - Roosevelt's Court Plan Statements, comments, 1937 (Box 92, Folder 75)
    - The Higher Learning, 1936-1937 (Box 92, Folder 76)
    - Proposed Brief: Nebbia v. New York, 1933-1934 (Box 92, Folder 77)
    - Constitutional Law, 1937 (Box 92, Folder 78)
    - Procedure: notes, 1939 (Box 92, Folder 79-80)
    - Manual on Federal Pleading, 1936 (Box 92, Folder 81)
    - Judicial Review of Administration, undated (Box 92, Folder 82)
    - West Publishing Co. Code Pleading, 3rd edition, 1956-1963 (Box 93, Folder 83-84)
    - Socialist Party Platforms and Leaflets, 1919-1920s (Box 93, Folder 85)
    - Conference of Commissioners on Uniform State Laws, Committee on Corpus and Law Uniform Income Apportionment Act, 1927-1933 (Box 93, Folder 86)
    - Conference of Commissioners on Uniform State Laws Committee on Corpus and Law Uniform Income Apportionment Act, 1927-1933 (Box 93, Folder 87)
    - Conference of Commissioners on Uniform State Laws Committee on Corpus and Law Uniform Income Apportionment Act, 1927-1933 (Box 93, Folder 88)
    - MacIntosh vs. United States, Citizenship case, 1930 (Box 93, Folder 89)
- United States Supreme Court Advisory Committee on Rules for Civil Procedure, 1935-1956; Series IV; 16' (38 boxes)
  The materials in Series IV are arranged in three chronological sections:
  1935-1939
  1943-1950
  1952-1956
  - 1935-1939
    - Advisory Committee on Rules for Civil Procedure: proceedings
      - 1935 November 14-17 (Box 94, Folder 1-4)
      - 1935 Nov 18, Vol 6 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - 1935 Nov 19, Vol 7 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - 1935 Nov 20, Vol 8 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - 1936 Feb 20, Vol 1 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - 1936 Feb 21, Vol 2 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - 1936 Feb 22, Vol 3 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - 1936 Feb 23, Vol 4 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - 1936 Feb 24, Vol 5 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - 1936 Feb 25, Vol 6 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - 1936 August 28-September 2 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - 1936 October 22-27 (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - 1937 February 1-4 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Advisory Committee on Rules for Civil Procedure: preparatory papers
      - Vol I, Tentative Draft I, 1935 Oct 15, 16, 25 (Box 97, Folder 17)
      - Vol II, Tentative Draft II, 1935 Dec-1936 Jan 15 (Box 98, Folder 18)
      - Vol III, Tentative Draft III, 1936 Mar (Box 98, Folder 19)
      - Vol IV, Preliminary Draft I, 1936 Apr (Box 99, Folder 20)
      - Vol V, Preliminary Draft II, 1936 Oct (photostat) (Box 99, Folder 21)
      - Vol VI, Preliminary Draft II, 1936 Oct 22 (mimeographed) (Box 99, Folder 22)
      - Vol VII, Preliminary Draft III, 1936 Dec-1937 Jan (Box 100, Folder 23)
      - Vol VIII, Preliminary Draft, 1937 Feb (Box 100, Folder 24)
      - Vol IX, Report, 1937 Apr 30 (Box 100, Folder 25)
      - Vol X, Rules, 1937 Nov (Box 101, Folder 26)
      - Vol XI, Rules (final changes) (Box 101, Folder 27)
      - Vol XII, Forms, 1936 (Box 101, Folder 28)
      - Vol XIII, Suggestions A-G, 1936 Jun-Dec (Box 101, Folder 29)
      - Vol XIV, Suggestions H-Z, 1936 Jun-Dec (Box 102, Folder 30)
      - Vol XV, Suggestions, 1937 Apr-Oct (Box 102, Folder 31)
      - Vol XVI, Abstracts, 1935 Oct-1937 Jan (Box 103, Folder 32)
      - Vol XVII, Abstracts, Report, 1937 Apr (Box 103, Folder 33)
      - Patent Law, Abstracts
      - Vol XVIII, American Bar Association Papers (Box 104, Folder 34)
      - Vol XIX, Transcripts of Meetings closed correspondence (Box 104, Folder 35)
      - Vol XX, Published Reports and Comments (Box 105, Folder 36)
      - Vol XXI, Committee Correspondence on Tent. Draft II, 1935 Dec-1936 Mar (Box 105, Folder 37)
    - Advisory Committee Correspondence
      - Vol XXII, 1936 Mar-1937 Jan (Box 106, Folder 38)
      - Vol XXIII, 1937 Feb-Dec (Box 107, Folder 39)
      - 1934 September-1935 October (Box 108, Folder 40-43)
      - 1935 November-1936 January (Box 109, Folder 44-49)
      - 1936 September-1937 April (Box 110, Folder 50-55)
      - 1937 May-1938 March (Box 111, Folder 56-60)
      - 1938 May-November (Box 112, Folder 61-64)
      - 1938 November-1939 September (Box 113, Folder 65-68)
    - Committee proceedings Dec 1939, memoranda (Box 113, Folder 69)
    - Correspondence and memoranda 1939-1942 (Box 113, Folder 70A)
    - Correspondence and memoranda (Box 113, Folder 70B)
  - 1943-1950
    - 1943 May 17-20 Proceedings
      - Vol 1 (Box 114, Folder 71)
      - Vol 2 (Box 114, Folder 72)
      - Vol 3 (Box 114, Folder 73)
      - Vol 4 (Box 114, Folder 74)
    - 1943 Oct 25-28 Proceedings
      - Vol 1 (Box 114, Folder 75)
      - Vol 2 (Box 114, Folder 76)
      - Vol 3 (Box 115, Folder 77)
    - 1944 Apr 3-5 Proceedings
      - Vol 1 (Box 115, Folder 78)
      - Vol 2 (Box 115, Folder 79)
      - Vol 3 (Box 115, Folder 80)
      - Vol 4 (Box 115, Folder 81)
      - Vol 5 (Box 115, Folder 82)
    - 1945 Jan-Feb Proceedings
      - Vol 1 (Box 115, Folder 83)
      - Vol 2 (Box 115, Folder 84)
      - Vol 3 (Box 116, Folder 85)
      - Vol 4 (Box 116, Folder 86)
      - Vol 5 (Box 116, Folder 87)
    - 1945 Apr-May Proceedings
      - Vol 1 (Box 116, Folder 88)
      - Vol 2 (Box 117, Folder 89)
      - Vol 3 (Box 117, Folder 90)
      - Vol 4 (Box 117, Folder 91)
      - Vol 5 (Box 117, Folder 92)
      - Vol 6 (Box 117, Folder 93)
    - 1946 Mar 25-28 Proceedings
      - Vol 1 (Box 118, Folder 94)
      - Vol 2 (Box 118, Folder 95)
      - Vol 3 (Box 118, Folder 96)
      - vol 4 (Box 119, Folder 97)
    - 1948 February 2-4 (Box 119, Folder 98)
    - 1950 April 6 (Box 119, Folder 99)
    - Tentative Draft I
      - pp. 1-109 (Box 120, Folder 100)
      - pp. 110-298 (Box 120, Folder 101)
      - pp. 298-377 (Box 120, Folder 102)
    - Proposed Amendments Jan 1949 (Box 120, Folder 103)
    - Proposed Amendments 1947, 1948 (Box 120, Folder 104)
    - Style Committee Draft 1946 (Box 120, Folder 105)
    - Proposed revision of Draft I 1945 (Box 120, Folder 106)
    - Preliminary Draft II May 1945 (Box 121, Folder 107)
    - Committee notes Apr 1945 (Box 121, Folder 108)
    - Correspondence, Preliminary Draft I May 1944 (Box 121, Folder 109)
    - Preliminary Draft III Feb 1944 (Box 121, Folder 110)
    - Preliminary Draft Apr 1944 (Box 121, Folder 111)
    - Preliminary Draft Apr 1944 (copy) (Box 122, Folder 112)
    - Amendments, Committee notes Jun 1943 (Box 122, Folder 113)
    - Correspondence
      - 1940-1942 (Box 122, Folder 114)
      - Memorandum 1942-1944 (Box 122, Folder 115)
      - 1943 (Box 122, Folder 116)
      - 1943 (Box 123, Folder 117)
      - Memorandum 1943 (Box 123, Folder 118)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 123, Folder 119)
    - Summary of comments on Preliminary Draft II Jan 1946 (Box 123, Folder 120)
    - Reporter's supplemental Mar 1946 (Box 123, Folder 121)
    - Correspondence, memorandum 1945 (Box 123, Folder 122)
    - Memorandum 1946 (Box 124, Folder 123)
    - Correspondence 1946 (Box 124, Folder 124)
    - Correspondence 1947-1951 (Box 124, Folder 125)
    - Memorandum 1943-1948 (Box 124, Folder 126)
    - Suggested amendment reforms 1944 (Box 124, Folder 127)
    - Suggested amendment reforms 1942 (Calif.) (Box 124, Folder 128)
  - 1952-1956
    - 1953 May 18-20 Proceedings
      - Vol 1 (Box 125, Folder 129)
      - Vol 2 (Box 125, Folder 130)
      - Vol 3 (Box 125, Folder 131)
    - 1954 Mar 24-26 Proceedings
      - Vol 1 (Box 126, Folder 132)
      - Vol 2 (Box 126, Folder 133)
      - Vol 3 (Box 127, Folder 134)
    - 1955 Mar 9-11 Proceedings
      - Vol 1 (Box 127, Folder 135)
      - Vol 2 (Box 127, Folder 136)
      - Vol 3 (Box 127, Folder 137)
    - Papers and amendment drafts
      - March 17 1950 (Box 128, Folder 138)
      - June 16 1952 (Box 128, Folder 139)
      - November 28 1952 (Box 128, Folder 140)
      - January-May 1953 (Box 128, Folder 141)
      - May 11 1953 (Box 128, Folder 142)
      - May 14 1953 (Box 128, Folder 143)
      - June 4 1953 (Box 128, Folder 144)
      - August 24 1953 (Box 128, Folder 145)
      - September 8 1953 (Box 128, Folder 146)
      - November 1953 (Box 128, Folder 147)
      - March 1954 (Box 128, Folder 148)
      - April-May 1954 (Box 128, Folder 149-150)
      - December 1954 (Box 128, Folder 151)
      - March 5 1955 (Box 128, Folder 152)
      - April-May 1955 (Box 128, Folder 153-154)
      - October 1955 (Box 128, Folder 155)
    - Papers
      - January 1952 (Box 128, Folder 156)
      - 1953 (Box 128, Folder 157)
      - March-August 1954 (Box 128, Folder 158)
      - September 1954 (Box 128, Folder 159)
      - October-November 1954 (Box 129, Folder 160)
      - November 1954 (Box 129, Folder 161)
      - December 1 1954 (Box 129, Folder 162)
      - December 15 1954 (Box 129, Folder 163)
      - December 30 1954 (Box 129, Folder 164)
      - January 5 1955 (Box 129, Folder 165)
      - January 11 1955 (Box 129, Folder 166)
      - January 28 1955 (Box 129, Folder 167)
      - January 31 1955 (Box 129, Folder 168)
      - February 3 1955 (Box 129, Folder 169)
      - February 11 1955 (Box 130, Folder 170)
      - February 28 1955 (Box 130, Folder 171)
      - March 1-4 1955 (Box 130, Folder 172-175)
      - March 8-9 1955 (Box 130, Folder 176-178)
      - March 23 1955 (Box 130, Folder 179)
      - April 5 1955 (Box 130, Folder 180)
      - June 6 1955 (Box 130, Folder 181)
      - June 10 1955 (Box 130, Folder 182)
      - June 17 1955 (Box 130, Folder 183)
      - August 11 1955 (Box 130, Folder 184)
      - October 5 1955 (Box 130, Folder 185)
      - March 27 1956 (Box 130, Folder 186)
    - Comparison of Civil Procedure Rules with Admiralty Rules 1952-1953 (Box 131, Folder 187)
    - Interlocutory appeals and the Federal Final Judgement Rule 1951-1952 (Box 131, Folder 188)
    - Correspondence and drafts 1955 (Box 131, Folder 189-190)
- Bibliography and writings, 1926-1968; Series V; 2" (1 box)
  - Charles E. Clark, A Bibliography by Solomon Smith Part 1, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Charles E. Clark, A Bibliography Part 2 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Charles E. Clark, A Bibliography Part 3 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Charles E. Clark, A Bibliography Part 4 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Articles, Miscellaneous, 1920s-1960s (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Speeches and Addresses Miscellaneous, 1929, 1934, 1958 (Box 132, Folder 6)
- Personal correspondence, memorabilia, family records, 1907-1967; Series VI; 4' (9 boxes)
  The materials in Series VI are arranged in ten sections:
  Personal correspondence 1915-1962
  Dorothy Clark correspondence 1955-1967
  Testimonials and resolutions in honor of C.E. Clark
  Photographs
  Law School exams
  School and professional memorabilia
  Biographical newspaper clippings
  Financial records
  Diplomas and awards
  - Personal Correspondence
    - 1915-1960 (Box 133, Folder 1-8)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Dorothy Clark Correspondence
    - Thurman Arnold (7), 1955-1967 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence relating to death of Charles E. Clark (Box 134, Folder 11)